[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Kot",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["개", "고양이", "새"],
        "correctanswer": "고양이",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Dzień Dobry",
        "correctanswer": "안녕하세요",
        "category": "Grammar"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Dom",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["집", "자동차", "나무"],
        "correctanswer": "집",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Jabłko",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["바나나", "사과", "포도"],
        "correctanswer": "사과",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Dobranoc",
        "correctanswer": "안녕히 주무세요",
        "category": "Grammar"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Czy możesz mi pomóc?",
        "correctanswer": "저를 도와줄 수 있나요?",
        "category": "Grammar"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Pies",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["개", "고양이", "쥐"],
        "correctanswer": "개",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Książka",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["책", "펜", "종이"],
        "correctanswer": "책",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Zielony",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["빨간색", "초록색", "파란색"],
        "correctanswer": "초록색",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Dziękuję",
        "correctanswer": "감사합니다",
        "category": "Grammar"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Proszę",
        "correctanswer": "제발",
        "category": "Grammar"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Rzeka",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["호수", "강", "바다"],
        "correctanswer": "강",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Woda",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["물", "주스", "우유"],
        "correctanswer": "물",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Dziecko",
        "type": "choice",
        "options": ["아이", "부모", "선생님"],
        "correctanswer": "아이",
        "category": "Vocabulary"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Gdzie jest toaleta?",
        "correctanswer": "화장실이 어디에 있나요?",
        "category": "Grammar"
    }
]
